<resources>
    <string name="app_name">myJobCard_Library</string>

    <!-- Status Change Alert messages-->
    <string name="noAlert"></string>
    <string name="enrouteAlert">You are leaving for job location. Do you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="arrivedAlert">Have you arrived at job location?</string>
    <string name="acceptAlert">You are accepting this job. Do you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="startAlert">You are starting this job. Do you want to continue?</string>

    <!-- Notification Status Change Alert messages-->
    <string name="notificationAcceptAlert">You are accepting this notification. Do you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="notificationRejectAlert">You are rejecting this notification. Do you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="notificationStartAlert">You are starting this notification. Do you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="notificationCompleteAlert">You are completing this notification. Do you want to continue?</string>

    <!-- Notification task/Item's task Status Change Alert messages-->
    <string name="notificationtaskCompleteAlert">You are completing this task. Do you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="notificationtaskStartAlert">You are starting this task. Do you want to continue?</string>

    <!--Attachments-->
    <string name="alertUploadFileSizeAboveLimit">File size should not be more than %1$s MB</string>
    <string name="alertDownloadSizeZeroErrorMsg">Something went wrong while downloading attachment. Please try to download again!</string>
    <string name="alertDownloadFailedErrorMsg">Something went wrong while downloading attachment. Error code: %1$s</string>
    <string name="msgNoFileFound">File not found on device!</string>
    <string name="msgNoApplicationFound">No supported application found to open this file!</string>

    <!--Pre checks-->
    <string name="msgTotalOperationRequiredToComplete">It is mandatory to complete all the pending operation. Current number of Incomplete operations are: %1$d</string>
    <string name="msgAtLeastOneOperationRequiredToComplete">It is mandatory to complete at least one pending operation.</string>
    <string name="msgTotalComponentsRequiredToIssued">It is mandatory to issue all the components. Currently un-issued components are: %1$d</string>
    <string name="msgAtLeastOneComponentRequiredToIssued">It is mandatory to issue at least one of the components %1$s.</string>
    <string name="msgAtLeastOneAttachmentRequired">It is mandatory to upload at least one attachment.</string>
    <string name="msgAllMandatoryFormsAreRequired">It is mandatory to submit all the required / mandatory forms for this Job.</string>
    <string name="msgAllMandatoryFormsAreRequiredToApprove">It is mandatory to Approve all the required / mandatory forms for this Job.</string>
    <string name="msgAllReadingPointsAreMandatory">It is mandatory to record all the readings for this Job.</string>
    <string name="msgAtLeastOneReadingPointRequired">It is mandatory to record at least one reading for this Job.</string>
    <string name="msgInspectionLotDecisionPending">User decision is pending for inspection lot %1$s.</string>
</resources>